Narrator: 1
F: We’re all stressed because we’re working to a tight schedule.
Narrator: 2
F: There’s space for three cars in their garage.
Narrator: 3
M: I only just had time to grab a sandwich.
Narrator: 4
M: I know I enjoyed the meal, but I can’t remember exactly what I ate.
Narrator: 5
M: She accused the media of harassment.
Narrator: 6
F: He couldn’t read the address on the envelope.
Narrator: 7
M: The others left the room to give us some privacy.
Narrator: 8
F: Her latest novel has caused a lot of controversy.
Narrator: 9
F: I don’t tend to go to the doctor’s very often.
Narrator: 10
F: She looked up as I entered the room.
Narrator: 11
M: It isn’t far to the station – just over a kilometre.
Narrator: 12
M: The course starts tomorrow and finishes on Friday.